<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biotop</title>
    <link>http://biotop.co/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Biotop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>biotop</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://biotop.co/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microscopy using Foldscopes</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-23/</guid>
      <description>Foldscope Workshop | 23.02.2019, 15:00 - 17:30 | Biotop Pop-Up Office, Gerbergasse 3, A-9500 Villach More spaces due to popular demand!!! Dive into an invisible world and experience the fascination of magnification. Together we are going to build microscopes out of paper and examine different samples from plants, animals and other tissues.
 Children and adults are equally welcome! Bring a smartphone and your foldscope (if you already have one).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microscopy using Foldscopes</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Foldscope Workshop | 02.02.2019, 15:00 - 17:30 | Biotop Pop-Up Office, Gerbergasse 3, A-9500 Villach Dive into an invisible world and experience the fascination of magnification. Together we are going to build microscopes out of paper and examine different samples from plants, animals and other tissues.
 Children and adults are equally welcome! Bring a smartphone and your foldscope (if you already have one). Fee: 15 Euro including a foldscope to take home with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Biotop</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/meet_biotop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/meet_biotop/</guid>
      <description>2018 has been an exciting and eventful year for Biotop. To celebrate this occasion and to provide a sneek peek into 2019, we&amp;rsquo;d like to cordially invite you to visit us in our temporary office at Gerbergasse 3 in Villach.
Starting at 6 pm, you can expect a program composed of a little look back at Biotop in 2018, and science slams by a neuroscientist, a molecular biologist, a fluid dynamics engineer and an archaeologist, who are coming to Villach especially for this occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop Christmas Calendar 2018</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/xmascal2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/xmascal2018/</guid>
      <description>Our &amp;ldquo;advent calendar&amp;rdquo; is finally on!
Every day, another aspect of Christmas will be used to explain science and design in an exciting and entertaining way. One will be able to discover what makes snowflakes scientifically exciting, why earworms such as “Last Christmas” drill so deep into our brains, what archaeologists find fascinating about gingerbread, and how architects approach gift-wrapping.
All the content will also be on display in the shop window of our office space at Gerbergasse 3 in Villach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Img</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/window-img/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 11:15:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/window-img/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Text</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/window-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 11:15:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/window-text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Biotop Meeting</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-october-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-october-2018/</guid>
      <description>On a sunny weekend at the end of October, we gathered at Groppenstein castle near Mallnitz-Obervellach in Carinthia for our third meeting.
  We welcomed three new additions to the group: Gerhard Dorn, Dieter Gutschi, and Ugne Greivyte. We started off with a recap of recent developments regarding the Container Lab project, as well as our participation in the London Design Festival. This was followed by a discussion of future plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biodesign Here Now - London Design Festival 2018</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/biodesign_here_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/biodesign_here_now/</guid>
      <description>We recently had the chance to be a part of the London Design Festival, by contributing to the &amp;ldquo;Biodesign Here Now&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the OpenCell campus in Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s Bush. We installed our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;, which we already had on display in Villach last Christmas.
  In addition, we conducted workshops in the Open Cell container lab that we designed the interior layout for and helped build back in May.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biodesign Here Now</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/biodesign_here_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/biodesign_here_now/</guid>
      <description>We are incredibly excited to be part of &amp;ldquo;Biodesign Here Now&amp;rdquo; at the London Design Festival 2018.
Exhibition opening hours are:
Wednesday to Thursday: 12 - 8.30 pm
Friday to Sunday: 12 - 11 pm
For a full list of events, please see here. In addition to presenting the exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;, Biotop will be hosting three workshops in the container lab at OpenCell on Saturday (22nd September 2018) at 4 pm (sign-up), 6 pm (sign-up) and 8 pm (sign-up) respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop X OpenCell - How to build a biolab in 10 days</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/opencell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/opencell/</guid>
      <description>We just got back from London, where we helped our friends at OpenCell furnish their first container lab.
How did this happen? Well, about a month ago we were contacted by Helene Steiner, who, together with Thomas Meany, is in the process of setting up a container village for small biotech startups in the heart of London. The idea is to provide a professional workspace (10 biolabs, 20 offices, 10 studios for artists and designers, 4 workshop containers, 1 store) to small businesses and startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the invisible - A peek behind the scenes</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-behind-scenes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-behind-scenes/</guid>
      <description>Here we would like to give you a peek behind the scenes of how we put together our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;. We came up with the concept and gathered together the individual contributions during our November meeting (read about it in this blog post).
Given that we all live in separate places, we had to find a good way of orangising and coordinating tasks remotely. We decided to use the project planning app &amp;ldquo;Trello&amp;rdquo; for this purpose and created an in silico plan for our exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the invisible - An exhibition by Biotop</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-catalogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-catalogue/</guid>
      <description>We are in the process of putting together a catalogue for our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;, which was on display in Villach from 22/12/2017 until 3/2/2018.
Watch this space.
Meanwhile, here are some pictures of the exhibits:
                   Photos: Andreas Körner &amp;amp; Anna Köferle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the Invisible III - Extended</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/see_the_invisible3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/see_the_invisible3/</guid>
      <description>Our exhibition has been running for a bit more than a month now. With more than 400 visitors, we count it as a great success.
We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce that our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the Invisible&amp;rdquo; will be extended! We&amp;rsquo;ll be open for 8 more evenings starting Friday, 26.01.2018 ending with a &amp;ldquo;finissage&amp;rdquo; on Saturday, 03.02.2018.
We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to seeing you there!
Opening hours:
 Fri, 26.01.2018 - 17:00-20:00 Sat, 27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the Invisible II</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/see_the_invisible2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/see_the_invisible2/</guid>
      <description>The Biotop exhibition “See the invisible - (Un)Sichtbares” will be open until 13th January 2018, Wednesday-Saturday, 5-8 pm. If you would like to visit outside the opening hours, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Container lab</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/project/container-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/project/container-lab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA barcoding</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/project/dna-barcoding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/project/dna-barcoding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the Invisible</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/see_the_invisible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/see_the_invisible/</guid>
      <description>The Biotop team invites you to join them for an evening of science and fun on 22nd December from 5 pm at Oberer Kirchenplatz 4 in Villach. Members of Biotop will present their work from a variety of disciplines ranging from basic science to archealogy, design and architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Biotop Meeting - November 2017</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-november-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-november-2017/</guid>
      <description>The second meeting of Biotopists took place in Vienna from 17th-19th November 2017. Over the course of three days we met at Spazio Pulpo to discuss progress and plan the Biotop Christmas event. Friday evening was dedicated to catching up. People arrived from various places - quite a few Biotop members live in Vienna, others had to travel from London, Oxford, Munich, and Villach. For those who hadn&amp;rsquo;t been able to attend the first Biotop meeting in July, this was the first time they met the other members of Biotop in person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop Kick-Off Meeting</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>So, this happened. The first ever Biotop meeting took place in Villach last weekend (28th-30th July 2017). Around 20 people who had each individually voiced their interest in joining the Biotop family but had (bar a few exceptions) never met in person descended on our small town to forge new friendships, set up collaborations and get some projects off the ground.
  People came to Villach from various different places including London, Oxford, Munich, Vienna, Graz, Salzburg (some participants from New York and Oxford joined the meeting online) and brought expertise in a variety of backgrounds with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop Kurzbeschreibung</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/short/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/short/</guid>
      <description>Wir sind Biotop, ein internationales Team von 25 jungen WissenschafterInnen und KünstlerInnen, das es sich zum Zeil gesetzt hat offener, disziplinenübergreifender Grundlagenforschung und Wissenschaftskommunikation ein Zuhause in Kärnten zu geben.
Als fachlich sehr diverse Gruppe, zu deren Forschungs- und Arbeitsbereichen derzeit Molekular- und Zellbiologie, Chemie, Neurowissenschaften, Physik, Statistik, Bioinformatik, Archäologie, Strömungslehre, Wirtschaftsgeschichte, Graphik, Design, Architektur, Literatur, Theater und Musik zählen, wissen wir um die spannenden Herausforderungen und dem Innovationspotential das disziplinenübergreifender Arbeit innewohnen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Lukas Hutter, MSc, DPhil (Oxon)  Eisenhammer Weg 2 / 58  A-9500 Villach  AUSTRIA
Freelance Scientist, Founder of Biotop*
 +43 664 455 60 76  lukas.hutter@biotop.co</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop Meeting</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/meeting-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/meeting-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>So, this happened. The first ever Biotop meeting took place in Villach last weekend (28th-30th July 2017). Around 20 people who had each individually voiced their interest in joining the Biotop family but had (bar a few exceptions) never met in person descended on our small town to forge new friendships, set up collaborations and get some projects off the ground.
  People came to Villach from various different places including London, Oxford, Munich, Vienna, Graz, Salzburg (some participants from New York and Oxford joined the meeting online) and brought expertise in a variety of backgrounds with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lukas Hutter</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/lukas-hutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 20:38:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/lukas-hutter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/new-website/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to welcome you to our new website! At the moment it is available in English and German, but we hope soon to be able to publish content in Slovenian and Italian as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participate</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/participate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/participate/</guid>
      <description>What does biotop offer to me? Science? - Not my cup of tea!
To many, science means that people with a liking of acronyms and white coats do things in sterile labs or with complex formulae; things with an air of importance; potentially groundbreaking things; things, which but a handful of people in the world understand. - And surly these people also share a love of clumsy acronyms, white labcoats and blackboards full of scribbles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you!</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/gratitude/</guid>
      <description>Sponsors Concept development is generously supported by the city of Villach.
  The first meeting in July was generously supported by
Il Gusto - Italian Deli / Rosegg Weingut Machherndl - Winery / Wachau AT
We&amp;rsquo;re currently actively looking for sponsors.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in becoming an sponsor, please get in touch with us!
Equipment Sponsors Through equipment sponsorships, private sponsors can support biotop through helping us finance individual pieces of lab equipent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dummy</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/project/color-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/project/color-quest/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastian Vasquez-Lopez</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/sebastian-vasquezlopez/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/sebastian-vasquezlopez/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexander Erlich</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/alexander-erlich/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/alexander-erlich/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andreas Körner</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/andreas-koerner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/andreas-koerner/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Resch</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-resch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-resch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Ritscher</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-ritscher/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-ritscher/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Wächter-Mittersteiner</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-waechter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-waechter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christine Marizzi</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/christine-marizzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/christine-marizzi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danai Dimitropoulou</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/danai-dimitropoulou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/danai-dimitropoulou/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herwig Scherabon</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/herwig-scherabon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/herwig-scherabon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Almagro-Garcia</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/jacob-almagro-garcia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/jacob-almagro-garcia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Fera</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/martin-fera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/martin-fera/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Schnabl</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/martin-schnabl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/martin-schnabl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Tatschl</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/michael-tatschl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/michael-tatschl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ursula Smole</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/ursula-smole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/ursula-smole/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolfgang Schütz</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/wolfi-schuetz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/wolfi-schuetz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ha Thi Hoang</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/ha-thi-hoang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:59:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/ha-thi-hoang/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Georg Fattinger</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/georg-fattinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:59:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/georg-fattinger/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ylli Qerkini</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/ylli-qerkini/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:59:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/ylli-qerkini/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korab Qerkini</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/korab-qerkini/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:58:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/korab-qerkini/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josef Ehgarter</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/josef-ehgarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:58:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/josef-ehgarter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mariangela Panniello</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/mariangela-panniello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:58:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/mariangela-panniello/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roberto Maffulli</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/roberto-maffulli/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 10:58:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/roberto-maffulli/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a.c.m.e,- (aek:mi)</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/acme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:38:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/acme/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About BIOTOP*</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/about-biotop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 14:10:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/about-biotop/</guid>
      <description>To many young scientists, the prospect of pursuing a career in academia has become a scary one. They&amp;rsquo;ve all seen idealistic young academics keen on changing how academia works from within, their grand ideas gradually stripped from them when attempting to balance personal and professional life while trying to meet the demands of tenure track committees and funding agencies.
Science is an endeavour that should be abound with idealism and innovative thinking, yet how come that so many young researchers have become so disillusioned nowadays?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BIOTOP* Mission Statement</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/about/</guid>
      <description>What? Biotop is an open collective of scientists engaging in the curiosity-driven, cross-disciplinary and collaborative translation of ideas; it is an experiment trying to reinvent the way we do science.
What does biotop offer to me? How can I participate? Why? Science and research are endeavours that should be abound with idealism and innovative thinking. Yet many young researchers are becoming increasingly disillusioned by the prospect of pursueing a career in academia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ralf Bliem</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/ralf-bliem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 11:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/ralf-bliem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Köferle</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-koeferle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 23:34:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/anna-koeferle/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niko Popitsch</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/niko-popitsch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 09:35:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/niko-popitsch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilian Rieder</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/person/kilian-rieder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 10:59:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/person/kilian-rieder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>