<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biotop Pop-Up Office, Gerbergasse 3, A-9500 Villach, Austria on Biotop</title>
    <link>http://biotop.co/en/places/biotop-pop-up-office-gerbergasse-3-a-9500-villach-austria/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Biotop Pop-Up Office, Gerbergasse 3, A-9500 Villach, Austria on Biotop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>biotop</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://biotop.co/en/places/biotop-pop-up-office-gerbergasse-3-a-9500-villach-austria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microscopy using Foldscopes</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-23/</guid>
      <description>Foldscope Workshop | 23.02.2019, 15:00 - 17:30 | Biotop Pop-Up Office, Gerbergasse 3, A-9500 Villach More spaces due to popular demand!!! Dive into an invisible world and experience the fascination of magnification. Together we are going to build microscopes out of paper and examine different samples from plants, animals and other tissues.
 Children and adults are equally welcome! Bring a smartphone and your foldscope (if you already have one).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microscopy using Foldscopes</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/foldscope-workshop_19-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Foldscope Workshop | 02.02.2019, 15:00 - 17:30 | Biotop Pop-Up Office, Gerbergasse 3, A-9500 Villach Dive into an invisible world and experience the fascination of magnification. Together we are going to build microscopes out of paper and examine different samples from plants, animals and other tissues.
 Children and adults are equally welcome! Bring a smartphone and your foldscope (if you already have one). Fee: 15 Euro including a foldscope to take home with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Biotop</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/event/meet_biotop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/event/meet_biotop/</guid>
      <description>2018 has been an exciting and eventful year for Biotop. To celebrate this occasion and to provide a sneek peek into 2019, we&amp;rsquo;d like to cordially invite you to visit us in our temporary office at Gerbergasse 3 in Villach.
Starting at 6 pm, you can expect a program composed of a little look back at Biotop in 2018, and science slams by a neuroscientist, a molecular biologist, a fluid dynamics engineer and an archaeologist, who are coming to Villach especially for this occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>