<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Biotop</title>
    <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Biotop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>biotop</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://biotop.co/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop Christmas Calendar 2018</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/xmascal2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/xmascal2018/</guid>
      <description>Our &amp;ldquo;advent calendar&amp;rdquo; is finally on!
Every day, another aspect of Christmas will be used to explain science and design in an exciting and entertaining way. One will be able to discover what makes snowflakes scientifically exciting, why earworms such as “Last Christmas” drill so deep into our brains, what archaeologists find fascinating about gingerbread, and how architects approach gift-wrapping.
All the content will also be on display in the shop window of our office space at Gerbergasse 3 in Villach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Biotop Meeting</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-october-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-october-2018/</guid>
      <description>On a sunny weekend at the end of October, we gathered at Groppenstein castle near Mallnitz-Obervellach in Carinthia for our third meeting.
  We welcomed three new additions to the group: Gerhard Dorn, Dieter Gutschi, and Ugne Greivyte. We started off with a recap of recent developments regarding the Container Lab project, as well as our participation in the London Design Festival. This was followed by a discussion of future plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biodesign Here Now - London Design Festival 2018</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/biodesign_here_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/biodesign_here_now/</guid>
      <description>We recently had the chance to be a part of the London Design Festival, by contributing to the &amp;ldquo;Biodesign Here Now&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the OpenCell campus in Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s Bush. We installed our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;, which we already had on display in Villach last Christmas.
  In addition, we conducted workshops in the Open Cell container lab that we designed the interior layout for and helped build back in May.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop X OpenCell - How to build a biolab in 10 days</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/opencell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/opencell/</guid>
      <description>We just got back from London, where we helped our friends at OpenCell furnish their first container lab.
How did this happen? Well, about a month ago we were contacted by Helene Steiner, who, together with Thomas Meany, is in the process of setting up a container village for small biotech startups in the heart of London. The idea is to provide a professional workspace (10 biolabs, 20 offices, 10 studios for artists and designers, 4 workshop containers, 1 store) to small businesses and startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the invisible - A peek behind the scenes</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-behind-scenes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-behind-scenes/</guid>
      <description>Here we would like to give you a peek behind the scenes of how we put together our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;. We came up with the concept and gathered together the individual contributions during our November meeting (read about it in this blog post).
Given that we all live in separate places, we had to find a good way of orangising and coordinating tasks remotely. We decided to use the project planning app &amp;ldquo;Trello&amp;rdquo; for this purpose and created an in silico plan for our exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the invisible - An exhibition by Biotop</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-catalogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/invisible-catalogue/</guid>
      <description>We are in the process of putting together a catalogue for our exhibition &amp;ldquo;See the invisible&amp;rdquo;, which was on display in Villach from 22/12/2017 until 3/2/2018.
Watch this space.
Meanwhile, here are some pictures of the exhibits:
                   Photos: Andreas Körner &amp;amp; Anna Köferle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Biotop Meeting - November 2017</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-november-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-november-2017/</guid>
      <description>The second meeting of Biotopists took place in Vienna from 17th-19th November 2017. Over the course of three days we met at Spazio Pulpo to discuss progress and plan the Biotop Christmas event. Friday evening was dedicated to catching up. People arrived from various places - quite a few Biotop members live in Vienna, others had to travel from London, Oxford, Munich, and Villach. For those who hadn&amp;rsquo;t been able to attend the first Biotop meeting in July, this was the first time they met the other members of Biotop in person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biotop Kick-Off Meeting</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/meeting-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>So, this happened. The first ever Biotop meeting took place in Villach last weekend (28th-30th July 2017). Around 20 people who had each individually voiced their interest in joining the Biotop family but had (bar a few exceptions) never met in person descended on our small town to forge new friendships, set up collaborations and get some projects off the ground.
  People came to Villach from various different places including London, Oxford, Munich, Vienna, Graz, Salzburg (some participants from New York and Oxford joined the meeting online) and brought expertise in a variety of backgrounds with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/new-website/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to welcome you to our new website! At the moment it is available in English and German, but we hope soon to be able to publish content in Slovenian and Italian as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About BIOTOP*</title>
      <link>http://biotop.co/en/blog/about-biotop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 14:10:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://biotop.co/en/blog/about-biotop/</guid>
      <description>To many young scientists, the prospect of pursuing a career in academia has become a scary one. They&amp;rsquo;ve all seen idealistic young academics keen on changing how academia works from within, their grand ideas gradually stripped from them when attempting to balance personal and professional life while trying to meet the demands of tenure track committees and funding agencies.
Science is an endeavour that should be abound with idealism and innovative thinking, yet how come that so many young researchers have become so disillusioned nowadays?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>